DAVID ZUNIGA

SOFTWARE & DATA ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I WOULD INTRODUCE MYSELF IN SIX WORDS.
PASSIONATE CODER, RESPONSIBLE, BEST COLLEAGUE
EVER. THAT PRETTY MUCH SUMS IT UP, THOUGH AT
LEAST THE LAST ONE MY FORMER COLLEAGUES HAVE TO
CONFIRM. I TRY TO DO A GOOD JOB IN ALL ROLES I HAVE
IN LIFE, AND I ENJOY THE PROCESS IMMENSELY. DO
YOU WANT ME TO TALK ABOUT MY CODING SKILLS AND
EXPERIENCE NOW, OR WILL WE DISCUSS IT LATER IN THE
INTERVIEW?

EXPERIENCE

IBM (2019 - 2021)

- Technical Support Engineer Apr 2019 to Nov 2019
- Centralize Technical Agent Nov 2019 to Feb
- 2021
- IBM
- · Backlog manager: Manage and report account backlog,
- Backlog data analysis using Python and reporting.
- Coordinate with different teams to work on new issues, priorities and special cases.
- Support to physical and virtual machines (Citrix) and
- servers (Azure and Google cloud) and configuration automation using Puppet.
- Backlog data analysis using service now, Python and MS Excel.

SERVER ENGINEER (2021)

- Avid/CSS February 2021 to Aug 2021
- Provide support to English-speaking users on issues
- with Avid production management tools and their functionality on Windows and Linux servers.
- Log analysis, tasks automation with Python and
- management and automation with Terraform and Jenkins.

CLOUD & DATA AUTOMATION ENGINEER (2021 - 2022)

- Equifax Aug 2021 to May 2022
- GCP and AWS task automation with Python, terraform, bash and data analysis. Report creation with HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Google Cloud Composer, Big Query and AirFlow.

PYTHON & DATA ENGINEER (2022 - PRESENT)

- CISCO/3 Pillar May 2022 to present
- Creating Python library for CISCO Firewalls configuration automation and testing.
- Data analysis and dashboard creation in PowerBI and HTML documents

FRONT-END ENGINEER (2019 - PRESENT)

- Freelance 2019 to present
- Web development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and ReactJs.
- API creation using Python and Flask.
- Tools: Shopify, WordPress, Elementor, Wix, Figma, Selenium (Python)

CONTACT

C:+506 83274231

E:JDAVID.ZUNIGAR@GMAIL.COM

GITHUB: DAVEZUNIGA

PORTFOLIO

EDUCATION

CENFOTEC

- INFRASTRUCTURE AND IT SUPERIOR TECHNICAL DEGREE.
- FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATION.
- ECCOUNCIL CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER CERTIFICATION.
- IT BACHELOR'S DEGREE.

COURSERA

- IBM CYBERSECURITY ANALYST PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE.
- GOOGLE IT AUTOMATION WITH PYTHON PROFESSIONAL

CERTIFICATE.

- JENKINS AUTOMATING YOUR DELIVERY PIPELINE.
- IBM AI ENGINEERING PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE (PYTHON).
- GOOGLE DATA ANALYTICS PROFESSIONAL

SKILLS

- \bullet PYTHON
- JAVASCRIPT
- SQL
- AUTOMATION
- AIRFLOW
- DATA ANALYTICS
- CYBERSECURITY
- JENKINS
- LINUX